{"da_array":[
	{
		"da_number": 1,
		"da_title": "Design Argument 1",
		"sections": [
			{
				"section_number":4,
				"section_title":"Describe the desire outcomes",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":9,
						"question_text":"What’s a real example of what a user wants to do? (concrete user class / scenario)",
						"question_answers": "da1_answer_9",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					},
					{
						"question_number":10,
						"question_text":"What should users do? (and what should happen when the do?)",
						"question_answers": "da1_answer_10",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":5,
				"section_title":"Describe core obstacles",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":11,
						"question_text":"Where can designs go wrong? What may prevent a user from reaching their goal?",
						"question_answers": "da1_answer_11",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":6,
				"section_title":"Describe the design intervention",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":12,
						"question_text":"What are the core characteristics of your design?",
						"question_answers": "da1_answer_12",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":7,
				"section_title":"Constructing arguments",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":13,
						"question_text":"Why would the design work?",
						"question_answers": "da1_answer_13",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":8,
				"section_title":"Write the design argument",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":14,
						"question_text":"What is your conceptual approach to solving the problem?",
						"question_answers": "da1_answer_14",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					},
					{
						"question_number":15,
						"question_text":"What is your design argument?",
						"question_answers": "da1_answer_15",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":9,
				"section_title":"Check your arguments",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":16,
						"question_text":"Will your design work? Is it novel?",
						"question_answers": "da1_answer_16",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"da_number": 2,
		"da_title": "Design Argument 1",
		"sections": [
			{
				"section_number":4,
				"section_title":"Describe the desire outcomes",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":9,
						"question_text":"What’s a real example of what a user wants to do? (concrete user class / scenario)",
						"question_answers": "da2_answer_9",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					},
					{
						"question_number":10,
						"question_text":"What should users do? (and what should happen when the do?)",
						"question_answers": "da2_answer_10",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":5,
				"section_title":"Describe core obstacles",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":11,
						"question_text":"Where can designs go wrong? What may prevent a user from reaching their goal?",
						"question_answers": "da2_answer_11",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":6,
				"section_title":"Describe the design intervention",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":12,
						"question_text":"What are the core characteristics of your design?",
						"question_answers": "da2_answer_12",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":7,
				"section_title":"Constructing arguments",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":13,
						"question_text":"Why would the design work?",
						"question_answers": "da2_answer_13",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":8,
				"section_title":"Write the design argument",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":14,
						"question_text":"What is your conceptual approach to solving the problem?",
						"question_answers": "da2_answer_14",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					},
					{
						"question_number":15,
						"question_text":"What is your design argument?",
						"question_answers": "da2_answer_15",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":9,
				"section_title":"Check your arguments",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":16,
						"question_text":"Will your design work? Is it novel?",
						"question_answers": "da2_answer_16",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"da_number": 3,
		"da_title": "Design Argument 1",
		"sections": [
			{
				"section_number":4,
				"section_title":"Describe the desire outcomes",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":9,
						"question_text":"What’s a real example of what a user wants to do? (concrete user class / scenario)",
						"question_answers": "da3_answer_9",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					},
					{
						"question_number":10,
						"question_text":"What should users do? (and what should happen when the do?)",
						"question_answers": "da3_answer_10",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":5,
				"section_title":"Describe core obstacles",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":11,
						"question_text":"Where can designs go wrong? What may prevent a user from reaching their goal?",
						"question_answers": "da3_answer_11",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":6,
				"section_title":"Describe the design intervention",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":12,
						"question_text":"What are the core characteristics of your design?",
						"question_answers": "da3_answer_12",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":7,
				"section_title":"Constructing arguments",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":13,
						"question_text":"Why would the design work?",
						"question_answers": "da3_answer_13",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":8,
				"section_title":"Write the design argument",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":14,
						"question_text":"What is your conceptual approach to solving the problem?",
						"question_answers": "da3_answer_14",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					},
					{
						"question_number":15,
						"question_text":"What is your design argument?",
						"question_answers": "da3_answer_15",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"section_number":9,
				"section_title":"Check your arguments",
				"section_updated":0,
				"questions":[
					{
						"question_number":16,
						"question_text":"Will your design work? Is it novel?",
						"question_answers": "da3_answer_16",
						"question_updated":0,
						"question_confidence":1
					}
				]
			}
		]
	}
]}